Three years ago,
Old Master Sheng was gravely ill.
On his deathbed, he gave orders
to find someone born with a
Pure Yin Destiny.
A son-in-law with this Destiny Chart
to avert a huge disaster for the Shengs.
And I,
am that very person.
How do you know this?
I also know
that The Four Great Families,
on the fifteenth of next month,
will all face a sudden disaster.
You are seeking the Dragon-Seeking Ruler
to help you locate the place
from twenty years ago,
that Tidal Tomb you all visited.
And I, this human shield,
am meant to ward off disaster and evil
for you along the way.
So, my dear mother-in-law,
you'd better be nice to me.
Otherwise,
a human shield like me...
The Mei and Wan families
are both fighting over me.
My dear son-in-law, what I said earlier...
was all just for the outsiders to hear.
How could we find fault with our own?
Alright.
Wait here for your friend
and come home early.
Mother will be waiting for you for dinner.
Holy crap.
"Waiting for you for dinner"?
Forget it.
I'd better just go back by myself.
You!
How did you get out?
That female ghost thought I was too ugly,
so she kicked me out.
Young Master, what were you mumbling about?
I was saying...
"waiting for you for dinner."
No, hold on.
We need to have a little chat before dinner.
Come on, take a seat.
I just don't get it.
That woman in red knelt to you,
and that little girl didn't dare approach.
Why was that?
Actually, it's just that
the metallic artifacts here
and rock structures created
an abnormal magnetic field,
causing past secret room images to replay.
Plus, it can interfere with human brain waves.
In fact, it was all fake.
I didn't get that, but it doesn't matter.
Young Master, if we sell this thing,
could we afford to get two wives?
The Dragon-Seeking Ruler!
You brought it out!
Great.
With this,
I can retrieve what I want, step by step.
What plan?
Becoming the Sheng son-in-law is step one.
The real show has just begun.
Did you hear?
That guy
tried to force himself on the young miss.
Talk about desperate.
More than just desperate.
He's a total pervert.
The Sheng family...
Have they already started?
Water Qi converges at the center.
Earth veins run southwest.
And then...
What are you mumbling, Young Master?
This is a fragment of the
Earth Vein Incantation Scripture.
It's used with the Dragon-Seeking Ruler.
Isn't the Earth Vein Incantation Scripture
the Sheng family's treasure?
How do you know it?
I just picked up a little bit by accident.
You... aren't you already dead?
I'm taking you down to keep me company.
Go to hell!
The outhouse is over there.
Don't let him get away!
If he falls in, we'll have to fish him out.
You said it.
We were really in sync back in that room.
One look and you knew what I wanted to do.
Then the master's room...
Go take a look.
Hope he didn't really go crazy from fear.
Master!
Don't kill me!
This...
Master!
What happened here?
Wake up, Master!
Master!
Don't scare me, Master!
Please, wake up!
Master!
Oh, Master!
Tiankun.
You're saying...
Sheng Qiufeng is dead?
He was scared to death. Such huge eyes!
No, wait.
Why go to his place so late at night?
I heard...
that good-for-nothing had the nerve
to go back to the Shengs.
If he talks about what we did
in the secret room,
it would be very bad for us.
As long as that kid is alive,
the Shengs have no reason
to divorce him right away.
If they don't divorce him,
how am I supposed to marry Ling Yu?
And if I can't marry Ling Yu,
how can my father take over the Shengs?
Got it, got it.
Or I could just...
I knew it.
So crude and low-class!
Look, don't we have the talisman book now?
The Fierce Ghost Talisman.
Even immortals would be scared to death,
let alone that little piece of trash.
Let me show you one first.
So ugly!
Boring.
Father.
The Sheng family head is dead.
Isn't this the perfect time
to take over the Shengs?
Keep dreaming.
Don't they still have a Young Master?
Young Master?
Father, now that you mention it,
all of this is way too coincidental.
Young Master.
People have been dying mysteriously
these past few years,
and now it's our family head's turn.
Instead of going to the mourning hall,
why are you wandering around here?
Look.
What does this mean?
Is there a tomb here?
Are we living on top of graves?
No, it's still over here.
Keep looking.